<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:padding="16dp"
    android:background="@drawable/background">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <!-- Add UI elements to display waste disposal tips, for example, TextViews or WebView -->
        <!-- Replace this with your desired content for waste disposal tips -->

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Waste Disposal Tips"
            android:textSize="24sp"
            android:textStyle="bold|italic"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:layout_marginTop="32dp" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:text="1. Reduce, Reuse, Recycle: Follow the three Rs – Reduce your waste generation, Reuse items whenever possible, and Recycle materials like paper, plastic, glass, and metal.

\n\n2. Composting: Create a compost pile for organic waste like fruit and vegetable scraps, coffee grounds, and yard trimmings. Composting enriches soil and reduces landfill waste.

\n\n3. Donate or Sell: Instead of throwing away items in good condition, consider donating to charities or selling them to reduce landfill waste.

\n\n4. Proper E-Waste Disposal: Dispose of electronic waste (e-waste) like old phones, computers, and batteries through proper recycling programs to prevent harmful chemicals from contaminating the environment.

\n\n5. Avoid Single-Use Plastics: Opt for reusable items like water bottles, cloth bags, and containers to reduce plastic waste.

\n\n6. Safe Medication Disposal: Follow proper guidelines for disposing of expired or unused medications to prevent them from entering water systems.

\n\n7. Hazardous Waste: Dispose of hazardous waste such as paints, solvents, and chemicals through designated collection centers to prevent pollution.

\n\n8. Proper Packaging Disposal: Break down and recycle cardboard boxes, rinse and recycle plastic containers, and dispose of packaging materials responsibly.

\n\n9. Buy in Bulk: Purchase products in bulk to reduce excessive packaging waste and save money.

\n\n10. Educate and Advocate: Spread awareness about waste management in your community and advocate for sustainable practices to encourage responsible waste disposal.

\n\nImplementing these waste disposal tips in your daily life can significantly contribute to reducing your environmental impact and promoting a healthier planet."
            android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
            android:textSize="12sp"/>

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>
